Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Why is he alone here?
لماذا هو وحيد هنا؟
Where are the others?
أين الباقين؟
Isn't he afraid of being eaten by the man-eating demon?
أليس خائفا من أن يأكله الشيطان آكل البشر؟
What if he's not human?
ماذا لو لم يكن إنسانا؟
He's a demon?
إنه شيطان؟
Oh my!
يا إلهي!
What would you like to ask, sir?
ماذا تريد أن تسأل يا سيدي؟
I, Master Ma,
أنا، سيدتي ما،
know astronomy above,
اعرف علم الفلك أعلاه،
geography below,
الجغرافيا أدناه،
and can change fate itself!
ويمكنه أن يغير القدر نفسه!
Sir, your forehead is full,
سيدي، جبهتك ممتلئة،
your eyes are bright,
عيناك مشرقة
you must be destined for wealth and longevity!
لا بد أن يكون مقدرًا لك الثروة وطول العمر!
You've come to the right person with Master Ma.
لقد أتيت إلى الشخص المناسب مع المعلم ما.
Tell me what you need.
أخبرني بما تحتاجه.
Long time no see,
وقت طويل لا رؤية،
you bootlicker.
أنت لاعق الأحذية.
Bootlicker?
لاعق الأحذية؟
How is it you?
كيف حالك؟
Come out now.
اخرج الآن.
You've forgotten me so quickly?
لقد نسيتني بهذه السرعة؟
How could I possibly forget you,
كيف يمكنني أن أنساك؟
Sister Shangguan?
الأخت شانجوان؟
Everyone knows
الجميع يعرف
you're the most powerful demon hunter in the world.
أنت أقوى صياد شياطين في العالم.
What brings you here?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
I've been behaving myself lately,
لقد كنت أتصرف بشكل جيد في الآونة الأخيرة،
following demon rules,
اتباع قواعد الشيطان،
not causing any trouble at all.
لا يسبب أي مشكلة على الإطلاق.
I know you've been behaving.
أعلم أنك كنت تتصرف بشكل جيد.
Aren't you supposed to know everything?
أليس من المفترض أن تعرف كل شيء؟
I need to ask you about something.
أريد أن أسألك عن شيء ما.
Ask?
بسأل؟
You scared me!
لقد اخافتني!
This must be your husband?
هل يجب أن يكون هذا زوجك؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Please tell me what you need,
من فضلك قل لي ما تحتاجه
I'll hold nothing back,
لن أخفي شيئا
and tell you everything I know.
وأخبرك بكل ما أعرفه.
Let me ask you,
دعني اسألك
what's been happening at the Zou family recently?
ماذا حدث في عائلة زو مؤخرًا؟
Is there a man-eating demon?
هل يوجد شيطان اكل الانسان؟
Yes, yes.
نعم نعم.
Oh no,
أوه لا،
you two aren't planning to capture the man-eating demon, are you?
أنتما لا تخططان للقبض على الشيطان آكل البشر، أليس كذلك؟
I strongly advise you both
أنصحكما بشدة
to be extremely careful.
أن تكون حذرا للغاية.
Cut the nonsense.
اقطع الهراء.
Tell us what you know.
أخبرنا بما تعرفه.
Please, have a seat.
من فضلك، اجلس.
Speaking of the Zou family,
بالحديث عن عائلة زو،
they're truly known by everyone,
إنهم معروفون حقًا للجميع،
famous throughout the land.
مشهورة في جميع أنحاء البلاد.
Master Zou
المعلم زو
is the wealthiest man in town.
هو أغنى رجل في المدينة.
He and his wife, Madam Wang Zou,
وهو وزوجته السيدة وانغ زو،
have quite a beautiful love story.
لدي قصة حب جميلة جدًا.
Back in the day,
في الماضي،
Madam Zou
السيدة زو
was the top courtesan in town.
كانت أفضل عاهرة في المدينة.
Her figure...
شخصيتها...
Get to the point.
انتقل إلى النقطة الرئيسية.
The couple has a daughter
الزوجان لديهما ابنة
named Zou Haitang.
اسمه زو هايتانج.
She came of age two years ago
لقد بلغت سن الرشد منذ عامين
and has remained unmarried.
وظلت غير متزوجة.
The Zou family has vast wealth
عائلة زو لديها ثروة هائلة
and dominates the region.
وتسيطر على المنطقة.
Miss Zou
الآنسة زو
is truly the apple of everyone's eye.
إنها حقا تفاحة عين الجميع.
Master Zou even
حتى المعلم زو
spent a fortune to build
أنفق ثروة لبناء
the Golden Embroidery Tower.
برج التطريز الذهبي.
This Miss Zou
هذه الآنسة زو
since birth
منذ الولادة
has lived in this Golden Embroidery Tower
لقد عاش في برج التطريز الذهبي هذا
and has never left it.
ولم يتركها أبدًا.
Except for her personal maids,
باستثناء خادماتها الشخصية،
no outsiders are allowed to enter.
لا يسمح بدخول الغرباء.
She is truly
إنها حقا
a sheltered young lady from a noble family who never steps outside.
سيدة شابة محمية من عائلة نبيلة لا تخرج أبدًا.
Miss Zou is as beautiful as a heavenly fairy.
إن السيدة زو جميلة مثل الجنية السماوية.
Master Zou has even
حتى المعلم زو لديه
arranged an excellent marriage for his daughter.
رتب زواجًا ممتازًا لابنته.
She is to be married to the son of the current prefect,
وسوف تتزوج من ابن المحافظ الحالي.
forming a prestigious alliance between their families.
تشكيل تحالف مرموق بين عائلتيهما.
But for some unknown reason.
ولكن لسبب غير معروف.
On the eve of the engagement,
في عشية الخطوبة،
Miss Zou suddenly died.
لقد ماتت السيدة زو فجأة.
Mrs. Zou,
السيدة زو،
devastated by the loss of her beloved daughter,
مدمرًا بفقدان ابنتها الحبيبة،
her hair turned white overnight.
تحول شعرها إلى اللون الأبيض بين عشية وضحاها.
Haitang.
هايتانج.
What's even more bizarre is that
والأمر الأكثر غرابة هو أن
Haitang,
هايتانج،
after Miss Zou's death,
بعد وفاة الآنسة زو،
she transformed into a terrifying man-eating monster
لقد تحولت إلى وحش مرعب يأكل البشر
wreaking havoc in the Zou household.
إحداث الفوضى في منزل زو.
First, she devoured her own mother.
أولاً، التهمت أمها.
Then,
ثم،
she ate the entire wedding procession
لقد أكلت موكب الزفاف بأكمله
and nearly consumed her own father too.
وكادت أن تلتهم والدها أيضًا.
In no time,
في أي وقت من الأوقات،
the entire street
الشارع بأكمله
was gripped by terror.
لقد كان في حالة من الرعب.
I don't know anything else.
لا أعرف أي شيء آخر.
I never thought this man-eating demon
لم أكن أعتقد أبدًا أن هذا الشيطان آكل البشر
would even devour his own parents.
حتى أنه كان يلتهم والديه.
Brother-in-law.
شقيق الزوج.
Please be extremely careful.
يرجى توخي الحذر الشديد.
Poor Master Zou,
المسكين السيد زو،
in a single night,
في ليلة واحدة،
lost both his beloved wife and daughter.
لقد فقد زوجته الحبيبة وابنته.
It's truly heartbreaking.
إنه أمر مفجع حقا.
How could there be such a coincidence?
كيف يمكن أن يكون هناك مثل هذه المصادفة؟
If he lost his wife and daughter,
إذا فقد زوجته وابنته،
shouldn't the Zou household be holding a funeral?
ألا ينبغي لعائلة زو أن تعقد جنازة؟
Why are there
لماذا يوجد هناك
festive lanterns hanging at the entrance?
الفوانيس الاحتفالية معلقة عند المدخل؟
I don't know about that, sir.
لا أعلم عن هذا يا سيدي.
Looks like we need to visit the Zou residence
يبدو أننا بحاجة لزيارة منزل زو
to investigate the situation ourselves.
للتحقيق في الوضع بأنفسنا.
My powers are too weak.
قدراتي ضعيفة للغاية.
I'm afraid I can't help with anything else.
أخشى أنني لا أستطيع المساعدة في أي شيء آخر.
Brother-in-law.
شقيق الزوج.
You two have such great powers,
لديكما قوى عظيمة
this minor man-eating demon should be no challenge for you.
لا ينبغي أن يشكل هذا الشيطان الصغير الذي يأكل البشر أي تحدي بالنسبة لك.
Heh heh,
ها ها ها
no need to waste words with him.
لا داعي لإضاعة الكلمات معه.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Brother-in-law,
شقيق الزوج،
the jianghu is vast,
الجيانجهو واسعة،
we may never meet again.
ربما لا نلتقي مرة أخرى.
Farewell.
وداع.
Heh heh heh.
ههه ههه هه.
You don't need to be so sad.
لا داعي لأن تكون حزينًا جدًا.
We'll have plenty of time
سيكون لدينا الكثير من الوقت
to get to know each other in the future.
للتعرف على بعضنا البعض في المستقبل.
It seems the Zou family
يبدو أن عائلة زو
is hiding something serious.
يخفي شيئًا خطيرًا.
How are we going to sneak in there?
كيف سنتمكن من التسلل إلى هناك؟
I'm not pretending to be your wife again.
أنا لا أتظاهر بأنني زوجتك مرة أخرى.
Not as a couple?
ليس كزوجين؟
Brother-in-law.
شقيق الزوج.
Follow me.
اتبعني.
Please come in, honored guests.
يرجى الدخول، أيها الضيوف الكرام.
The clothes at our Jinxiu Pavilion
الملابس في جناح جينكسيو الخاص بنا
are among the finest in the city.
من بين الأفضل في المدينة.
However,
لكن،
I'm not sure if
أنا لست متأكدا إذا كان
you've brought enough silver.
لقد جلبت ما يكفي من الفضة.
Little pig demon.
شيطان الخنزير الصغير.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
How did you know I'm a demon?
كيف عرفت أنني شيطان؟
I forgot for a moment.
لقد نسيت للحظة.
You don't know me yet at this point.
أنت لا تعرفني حتى الآن.
It doesn't matter.
لا يهم.
We're demon hunters.
نحن صيادو الشياطين.
But don't worry,
ولكن لا تقلق،
we're here to catch another demon,
نحن هنا للقبض على شيطان آخر،
not you.
ليس انت.
Bring out your most expensive
أخرج أغلى ما لديك
and finest items.
وأرقى العناصر.
Right away!
فورا!
This outfit of yours
هذا الزي الخاص بك
needs to be paired with this hairpin
يجب أن يتم إقرانه مع دبوس الشعر هذا
to be perfect.
أن تكون مثاليًا.
However,
لكن،
this hairpin is quite expensive.
هذا دبوس الشعر باهظ الثمن إلى حد ما.
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
Not bad.
ليس سيئًا.
I like it.
أحبها.
Please wrap up all these items for me too.
من فضلك قم بتغليف كل هذه العناصر بالنسبة لي أيضًا.
Right away.
فورا.
Hey, wait.
مهلا، انتظر.
Shopkeeper.
صاحب متجر.
We can't carry all these purchases.
لا يمكننا أن نحمل كل هذه المشتريات.
Let's focus on our main task first.
دعونا نركز على مهمتنا الرئيسية أولا.
Do you need anything else?
هل تحتاج أي شيء آخر؟
Let me borrow this.
دعني أستعير هذا.
Oh my!
يا إلهي!
Please take pity on me.
من فضلك ارحمني.
My hometown was struck by disaster.
لقد ضربت الكارثة مدينتي.
I haven't had a drop of water for 7 days.
لم أشرب قطرة ماء لمدة 7 أيام.
I heard Master Zou is a generous man.
سمعت أن السيد زو رجل كريم.
Could you spare me a bite to eat?
هل يمكنك أن تعطيني لقمة لأكلها؟
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Master Zou.
المعلم زو.
Mind your manners.
انتبه لأخلاقك.
Sir.
سيد.
This poor child.
هذا الطفل المسكين.
Judging by your age,
استنادا إلى عمرك،
you're about the same age as my daughter.
أنت في نفس عمر ابنتي تقريبًا.
I simply can't bear to see you suffer.
لا أستطيع أن أتحمل رؤيتك تعاني.
Come,
يأتي،
please get up.
من فضلك قم .
Wait.
انتظر.
Do you really think
هل تعتقد حقا
she's an ordinary girl?
هل هي فتاة عادية؟
Then who is she?
إذن من هي؟
Who are you two?
من انتما الاثنان؟
We were passing by
كنا نمر
and sensed demonic energy in your home.
وأحسست بالطاقة الشيطانية في منزلك.
Would it be convenient
هل سيكون ذلك مناسبا؟
for us to enter and investigate?
لكي ندخل ونتحقيق؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Masters,
الماجستير،
please follow me.
من فضلك اتبعني.
It's all my fault.
إنه خطئي كله.
It's all my fault indeed.
إنه خطئي بالفعل.
Every day,
كل يوم،
I've only focused on my business
لقد ركزت فقط على عملي
and failed to take care of the mother and daughter.
وفشل في رعاية الأم وابنتها.
My condolences, Mr. Zou.
تعازيّ لك يا سيد زو.
No one can predict accidents.
لا أحد يستطيع التنبؤ بالحوادث.
It's such a pity.
إنه أمر مؤسف للغاية.
My precious daughter,
ابنتي العزيزة
whom I raised for fifteen years,
الذي ربيته لمدة خمسة عشر عامًا،
is gone just like that.
لقد ذهب هكذا تماما.
Fifteen years?
خمسة عشر عاما؟
As far as I know,
بقدر ما أعرف،
Miss Zou had her coming-of-age ceremony two years ago.
أقامت السيدة زو حفل بلوغها سن الرشد منذ عامين.
She should be 17 this year.
ينبغي أن تكون عمرها 17 عامًا هذا العام.
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
17 years old.
17 سنة.
The prime of her youth at 17,
ذروة شبابها في سن 17،
and she never got to enjoy it.
ولم تحظى بالمتعة أبدًا.
She just...
إنها فقط...
Please don't be too sad.
من فضلك لا تحزن كثيرا.
The most urgent matter now
الأمر الأكثر إلحاحًا الآن
is to catch the man-eating demon
هو القبض على الشيطان آكل البشر
to prevent it from harming more people.
لمنعها من إيذاء المزيد من الناس.
Ah, right.
اه، صحيح.
Yes, yes, yes.
نعم، نعم، نعم.
Masters,
الماجستير،
please quickly
من فضلك بسرعة
rid my home of this demon.
تخلص من هذا الشيطان في منزلي.
I've prepared fine quarters
لقد أعددت أماكن إقامة جيدة
and delicious meals for you.
ووجبات لذيذة لكم.
Why don't
لماذا لا؟
you both rest today?
هل تريدان الراحة اليوم؟
Thank you, sir.
شكرا لك سيدي.
Innkeeper,
صاحب النزل،
don't you think this Mr. Zou
ألا تعتقد أن هذا السيد زو؟
seems a bit suspicious?
يبدو مشبوهًا بعض الشيء؟
Tell me more.
أخبرني المزيد.
Think about it.
فكر في الأمر.
His wife and daughter just died,
لقد ماتت زوجته وابنته للتو،
yet he's still wearing gold and silver jewelry.
ومع ذلك فهو لا يزال يرتدي المجوهرات الذهبية والفضية.
He pretends to be sad,
يتظاهر بالحزن
but still puts effort into his appearance.
لكن لا يزال يبذل جهدًا في مظهره.
And also,
وأيضا،
he's known as a loving father,
ومن المعروف أنه أب محب،
yet he forgot his own daughter's age.
ولكنه نسي عمر ابنته.
That's clearly suspicious.
من الواضح أن هذا مثير للريبة.
You're not so stupid after all.
أنت لست غبيًا على الإطلاق.
Of course.
بالطبع.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
If there's something wrong, he'll slip up eventually.
إذا كان هناك شيء خاطئ، فإنه سوف ينزلق في نهاية المطاف.
We'll know when we catch him.
سوف نعرف عندما نقبض عليه.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
This Mr. Zou
هذا السيد زو
is truly a wealthy merchant.
هو تاجر ثري حقا.
The room he prepared for us
الغرفة التي أعدها لنا
is really nice.
إنه لطيف حقا.
Innkeeper,
صاحب النزل،
there's even a bathtub in here
حتى أن هناك حوض استحمام هنا
with hot water already in it.
مع الماء الساخن الموجود فيه بالفعل.
I'm going to take a bath.
سأذهب للاستحمام.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Taking a bath.
الاستحمام.
I'm still here.
أنا لا أزال هنا.
If you want to bathe, go somewhere else.
إذا كنت تريد الاستحمام، اذهب إلى مكان آخر.
Don't forget.
لا تنسى.
We're cultivation partners now.
نحن شركاء في الزراعة الآن.
If I leave now,
إذا غادرت الآن،
people will think we're not getting along.
الناس سوف يعتقدون أننا لا نتفق.
That I'm inadequate.
أنني غير مناسب.
It'll affect our mission later.
وسوف يؤثر ذلك على مهمتنا في وقت لاحق.
Who dares to say that about me?
من يجرؤ على قول ذلك عني؟
I'll break their legs.
سأكسر أرجلهم.
Oh my.
أوه يا إلهي.
Don't be angry.
لا تغضب.
I'll just take the loss.
سأتحمل الخسارة فقط.
Who's there?
من هناك؟
Don't come in and see me!
لا تأتي لرؤيتي!
So comfortable.
مريح للغاية.
Boss.
رئيس.
I've been working with you for a while now.
لقد عملت معك لفترة من الوقت الآن.
How do you think I'm doing?
كيف تعتقد أنني أفعل؟
Very well.
جيد جدا.
I think I'm doing very well too.
أعتقد أنني أفعل جيدا جدا أيضا.
I think I'm
أعتقد أنني
fairly good-looking.
حسن المظهر إلى حد ما.
I'm perceptive.
أنا مدرك.
Most importantly,
والأهم من ذلك كله،
I'm capable.
أنا قادر.
And obedient too.
ومطيع أيضاً.
Don't you agree?
ألا توافق؟
So I think
لذلك أعتقد
you should treat me better from now on.
ينبغي عليك أن تعاملني بشكل أفضل من الآن فصاعدا.
How can there be good employees without good bosses?
كيف يمكن أن يكون هناك موظفين جيدين دون رؤساء جيدين؟
Right?
يمين؟
Boss, are you listening?
يا رئيس، هل تستمع؟
Where are my clothes?
أين ملابسي؟
Boss.
رئيس.
Shanguan Feiye.
شانجوان فيي.
Weren't you just singing your own praises?
ألم تكن فقط تغني مديحك لنفسك؟
Handle this small matter yourself.
تعامل مع هذه المسألة الصغيرة بنفسك.
Boss.
رئيس.
I've been thinking it over
لقد كنت أفكر في الأمر
and can't sleep in the middle of the night.
ولا أستطيع النوم في منتصف الليل.
Masters,
الماجستير،
why don't we find a place to hide first?
لماذا لا نجد مكانًا للاختباء أولاً؟
Just waiting here
فقط انتظر هنا
is too dangerous.
أمر خطير للغاية.
The man-eating demon has powerful magic.
الشيطان آكل الإنسان لديه سحر قوي.
Hiding anywhere would be useless.
الاختباء في أي مكان سيكون بلا فائدة.
Rather than waiting for death,
بدلا من انتظار الموت،
we should face the enemy head-on.
ينبغي علينا مواجهة العدو وجهاً لوجه.
Okay.
تمام.
All right.
حسنًا.
She's coming.
إنها قادمة.
She's here.
إنها هنا.
Protect the master!
حماية السيد!